fbdownloader.com 2012-09-14

# I

**_PRIVACY POLICY_**

Our business name is **HTTO Group, Inc (“Company”)**. We are the owner of our web site, [www.FBDownloader.com](http://www.fbdownloader.com/). All information provided in this Privacy Policy pertains to **HTTO Group, Inc** and [www.FBDownloader.com](http://www.fbdownloader.com/).

**_I.        General_**

A.       FBDownloader takes User privacy seriously and takes reasonable efforts to protect your privacy. We have created this _Privacy Policy (“Policies”)_ in order to share with you our information collection and use practices. **AS MORE CLEARLY DEFINED HEREIN, WE WILL NEVER KNOWINGLY SELL OR ASSIGN YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITHOUT YOUR KNOWLEDGE AND OR APPROVAL. Please read these _Policies_ carefully before sharing any personally identifiable information described below.**

B.       These _Policies_ apply solely to the web site located at [www.FBDownloader.com](http://www.fbdownloader.com/) (“web site”). Since Internet technologies are constantly evolving, these _Policies_ are subject to change at any time and any changes will be posted on this page. 

C.      These _Policies_ work hand-in-hand with the _Terms of Use_ , found elsewhere on the FBDownloader web site as well as the End-User License Agreement (EULA) for the FBDownloader Software Application.

**_II.     Definitions_** ****

The following words used in these _Policies_ shall have the following meanings:

          1\.       **" _Personal Information_ "** shall mean all data and/or information provided by and about User.

          2\.       **"HTTO web site"** shall mean all web sites on which **FBDownloader** is available for purchase and/or download.

          3\.       **"HTTO User"** shall mean all Users of the **FBDownloader** web site.

          **4.       "HTTO Products and Services"** shall mean the **FBDownloader Software Application.**

**      ****5.** **       "Registration Information"** shall mean the Personal Information Users are required to give to **HTTO** in the registration process, in order to access our services.

     6.       “ **Paid Version” & “Free Version” ****shall mean the two versions of the FBDownloader Software Application. The “Free Version” may be freely distributed, but it contains advertising messages from third-party advertisers. The “Paid Version” is distributed after payment by User, and it contains no advertising messages from third-party advertisers.**

**_III.    **What Personally Identifiable Information Does HTTO Collect and How Is It Used?**_**

A.       In order to download and use the Paid Version, you will be asked for certain personally identifiable information such as name, email address, shipping and billing address and Paypal payment information. _For example_ , when you create an Account, the information you provide may be used by us to communicate with you in the future. 

B.       FBDownloader will not collect personally identifiable information from Users while they use the web site or the FBDownloader Software Application, unless you voluntarily provide it to us or authorize us to collect such information. When you use the FBDownloader Software Application, we may collect information about the pages and advertisements you view. For example, we may collect information about page views, impressions and clicks, as well as similar web usage information. Also, general information about your browser and your computer’s operating system, the cookie number or other identifying alphanumerical information, enabling us to identify your computer and the date and time the above information is logged. FBDownloader may also collect information about the online advertisements that are displayed on the web sites you visit, such as the text, source and URL of the advertisement

C.      FBDownloader may use or disclose User’s personally identifiable information to:

          1\.       operate and manage the web site;

          2\.       provide products/services that have been requested by User; or

          3\.       respond to other inquires or requests by User. 

D.      We may disclose User’s personally identifiable information in the establishment or exercise of legal rights or defenses against legal claims, to comply with applicable laws or regulations, to comply with a valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order or to investigate suspected fraud or a violation of our _Terms of Use_. We will never sell User Information to any third party not affiliated with HTTO, without consent, except in connection with the sale or merger of HTTO or the division responsible for such services provided.

E.       HTTO may also use such information for marketing their products and services to you **_ONLY IF_** you have not ‘opted out’ to receive such marketing information from us. 

F.       HTTO may, from time to time, send or post surveys or requests for User feedback in order to help us make our web site and services better. Any responses we receive from Users will be used only to evaluate our web site and services and no personally identifiable information from Users will be shared with any non-employees of HTTO. 

G.      FBDownloader may, from time to time, send notices about special offers, promotions or contests. If you sign up to participant in any of these, we will collect your email address. If you are chosen for a promotion or as a winner in a contest, you give FBDownloader permission to use your name, image and other information about you, for marketing purposes.

**_IV._** _     **What Non-Personally Identifiable Information Do We Collect and How Is It Used?**_

A.       HTTO does collect and track certain non-personally identifiable information, including, but not limited to, IP numbers and browser type, access times, domain names, usage habits and other information which does not specifically identify any individual. 

B.       HTTO may use and disclose non-personally-identifiable information for any number of reasons, including but not limited to, working with business partners and improving our web site and services. 

C.      HTTO collects demographic information from you, including gender, age and location data, for the purpose of selecting suitable advertising messages used in the Free Version of the FBDownloader Software Application.  This demographic information is not sold nor provided to any third-party, under any circumstances. HTTO may also collect usage data on a periodic basis from Users.  This usage data is collected by HTTO in order to improve our products and services to Users

**_V.      Does HTTO Offer Forums, Chatrooms and Groups?_** ****

HTTO does not offer Forums or User Feedback at this time. If Users wish to provide Feedback to HTTO regarding the FBDownloader Software Application, User may send a message to [Support@FBDownloader.com](mailto:Support@FBDownloader.com).

**_VI.     Can I Invite Friends & Family?_** ****

All FBDownloader Users are encouraged to freely distribute the Free Version of the FBDownloader Software Application and may invite new Users to discover both versions of the application. 

**_VII.   _****_Does HTTO Use_** _**Cookies?**_

A.       HTTO uses cookies and other technologies, such as pixel tags, to track traffic flow and patterns of travel within, and through, our web site. The Applications we distribute also use cookies to provide us with retention and usage information and to store user preferences. 

B.       Cookies are a standard Internet technology that allows us to store and retrieve login information on a User's computer or other electronic device.  Our server automatically asks a new User's browser whether it will accept our cookie file. If the cookie is accepted, our server will record the cookie's unique ID for our use in internal reporting. Every time the User returns to the web site or uses our Applications, we will be able to read that cookie's ID number and, among other things, can customize the services we deliver, based on the User's past preferences. 

C.      If a User accepts our cookie, but later wants to remove it, it can be deleted through User’s web browser. 

D.      _Cookies & web beacons_ may be used by our third-party advertisers to identify you.

E.       HTTO does not use _cookies_ to store information such as Paypal payment information, telephone numbers, or other information you provide. To maintain your privacy, you can disable your browser's ability to accept _cookies,_ but doing so may affect your ability to access and navigate our web site.

F.       Our third-party advertisers may use _cookies & web beacons_ on your computer in order to identify you to their servers. We have no access to or control over these _cookies or web beacons,_ hence, we will not be responsible for their use or misuse.

G.      This _Policy_ covers the use of _cookies & web beacons_ by AAndex. It does not cover the use of _cookies & web beacons _by any other third-party advertiser.

**_VIII.  Is My Information Private With FBDownloader Advertisers?_**

A.       Each of our third-party advertiser web sites (in the Free Version of the application) may have a _Privacy Policy_ that differs from that of HTTO. The privacy practices of third-party advertisers are not covered by our _Privacy Policy_. 

B.      

When you use the Free Version of the FBDownloader Software Application, you will see advertisements that are periodically updated. These advertisement messages typically come from third-party advertisement servers or advertisement networks. 

    C.         The ‘free version’ of FBDownloader may contain advertisements that, when clicked, take you to Internet sites managed by third parties. By activating these links, you are no longer using the FBDownloader Software Application.  FBDownloader has no control over Internet sites owned by third parties. These sites are managed entirely by third parties and FBDownloader cannot make any declaration whatsoever concerning the quality or overall content thereof, nor regarding the quality of the products offered, or the security of performing transactions on the sites in question. The fact that third party sites are identified on the FBDownloader Software Application should not, in any way, be interpreted as an endorsement by HTTO.

FBDownloader cannot be held liable for possible damages arising from the use of such third party sites. All complaints about third party sites should be addressed to the administrators of those sites.

    D.         Some of these advertising networks may place a persistent cookie on your computer in order to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement message. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by an online server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by an online server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

    E.         Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. Note that the FBDownloader Software Application does not use cookies, and does not have access to the cookies that may be placed by the third-party advertising servers or networks. 

    F.         Advertising messages displayed in the ‘Free Version’ of the FBDownloader Software Application may contain electronic images known as Web Beacons - sometimes called ‘single-pixel gifs’ - in order to help compile aggregated statistics and determine the effectiveness of promotional campaigns. We prohibit Web Beacons in advertisements displayed in the ‘Free Version’ of the FBDownloader Software Application from being used by third parties to collect or access your personal information.

    G.         Finally, HTTO may work with other companies that advertise in the ‘Free Version’ of the FBDownloader Software Application, in order to place Web Beacons on their web sites, in order to allow us to develop statistics on how often clicking on an advertisement in our application results in a purchase or other action on the advertiser's web site. In these ways, HTTO and the advertising networks may compile information about what advertisements are seen in the ‘Free Version’ of the FBDownloader Software Application and determine which advertisements are clicked on by Users. In addition, advertising messages may be stored on your computer for display while you are offline. 

    H.         HTTO may compile information about what advertising messages are seen in the ‘Free Version’ of the FBDownloader Software Application, and determine which advertising messages are clicked on and may share that information with advertising networks. This information allows an advertising network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. HTTO may use demographic information collected from you during the registration process (including age, location and gender data) to target advertisements that we believe will be of most interest to you. ** _IX.       What About Data Security?_** 

A.       To ensure the security of your data, including address information, HTTO always uses industry-standard encryption technologies (256kb _Secure Socket Layer_ – SSL) when transferring and receiving User data on our web site. 

B.       HTTO has instituted appropriate security measures that protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from Users. 

C.      HTTO requires that our third-party advertisers ensure the security of the data that Users provide to them, however, in the event of a breach of their security measures, User agrees that HTTO will not be liable for any loss or damage to you.

D.      HTTO limits access to personal information about Users to employees for whom we reasonably believe it is necessary, in order to provide products or services. 

E.       HTTO has physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with international regulations to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our web site.

F.       United States Electronic Communications Privacy Act Notice (18USC 2701-2711):  **HTTO makes no guaranty of confidentiality or privacy of any communication or information transmitted on the FBDownloader web site or any web site linked to the FBDownloader web site**. FBDownloader will not be liable for the privacy of email addresses, registration and identification information, disk space, communications, confidential or trade-secret information, or any other Content stored on HTTO equipment, transmitted over networks accessed by the FBDownloader web site or otherwise connected with User’s use of our service.

**_X._** _      **Can I** **Opt** **- out?**_

A.       HTTO gives you the option to remove your personally identifiable information from our list of active Users by completely uninstalling the FBDownloader Software Application from your computer or electronic device and deleting it from your Facebook applications.

B.       You may also choose to opt-out of certain communications from HTTO, such as software updates.

C.      All requests for unsubscribing or opting-out should be made by sending an email to Customer Support at [Support@FBDownloader.com](mailto:Support@FBDownloader.com). We will respond within 24 hours. 

D.      HTTO is not responsible for removing your personally identifiable information from the lists of any third-party advertiser who has previously been provided your information in accordance with this _Policy._   

**_XI._** _     **Where Is The** **Web Site** **Located?**_

The FBDownloader web site is maintained from within Israel. If you are located outside of Israel, by using our web site, you authorize the export of personally identifiable information to Israel, and its storage and use as specified in these _Policies_. **_XII.   What Is The Minimum Age To Use The FBDownloader Web Site?_** ****

A.       Use of the FBDownloader web site and HTTO products/services are intended for persons who are thirteen (13) years or older. If anyone between the ages of thirteen (13) and seventeen (17) years obtains access to our web site services and/or products, it is understood that it is specifically done with the consent, approval and authorization of such persons’ parents or legal guardians. Parents and legal guardians are responsible for their children's privacy and safety and should monitor their use of the Internet on a continuing basis. Under no circumstances will HTTO knowingly allow a person under the age of thirteen (13) years to register, even with the parents’ or legal guardian’s consent, approval or authorization.

B.       If proof comes to the attention of HTTO that a registered User is under the age of thirteen (13) years, and is accessing our services and/or products without the consent, approval or authorization of their parents or legal guardian, HTTO will immediately terminate such account  

**_XIII. Will There Be Changes to these _Policies?__** ****

A.       HTTO reserves the right to amend these _Policies_ at any time, in the event that this becomes necessary after their initial release, or in the event that it becomes necessary with respect to additional or amended services provided by HTTO. 

B.       HTTO will not personally notify you of any amendments or modifications to these _Policies_. **Users are urged to check these _Policies_ frequently in order to determine whether any changes have been made. Users understand and agree that continued use of the FBDownloader Software Application and the web site assumes that they have read and accepted these _Policies,_ as may be amended or modified from time to time.**

**_XIV.   Where Can I Access These _Policies__** ****

These _Policies_ are accessible from the Home Page of the FBDownloader web site, at [www.FBDownloader.com](http://www.fbdownloader.com/), under the link _“Privacy Policy”._

**_XV.    Section Titles_**

The section titles used in these _Policies_ are purely for convenience and carry with them no legal or contractual effect.

**_XVI.   What is the Effective **Date of These _Policies?_**_**

**These _Policies_ were last updated on April 20, 2012.**
